hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jeremy
Krakowski and today I'm going to be
talking about how coaches and course
creators can get better results with
something that I've been teaching a lot
about and that's how we need to break up
with hesitation
and we have to get to the root of why we
hesitate
if you're somebody who feels like you
want to build a coaching or course
business
um
you may get overwhelmed by some of the
technology and you might feel like oh
it's scary to use stuff that I've never
used before
but it's a requirement for you to
actually learn to use that technology if
you want to be successful in your
coaching or course business your Supreme
priority
is not delivering your coaching it's
it's actually
you
marketing and selling what you have to
offer that's the supreme goal of your
efforts
your coaching and the actual delivery of
your course and your coaching comes
secondary to that
once you get that and you realize that
you can go out there and you start to
grow your email list you got to make a
page on a website where people put in
their name and email address
and so those are just the two things
that I want to invite you to stop
hesitating on
so much if you're listening to this
podcast making a page where people sign
up
and you writing offer copy and sales
copy to draw in people to promote using
paid advertising some kind of a zoom
call like a free Zoom call that people
can hop onto and then you could sell
them whether it be to schedule a call
with you or a program that you have for
sale
this is the best funnel to use by the
way this is what we're using right now
generating four hundred thousand dollars
in the last four months in our business
so
sit with inside of you for just a moment
that part of you that feels we're just
going to go right into it that feels
like
scared to use technology maybe you had
somebody in your life make you feel
stupid because you didn't know how it
worked or maybe something didn't work
out well and it cost you money or it
made you feel embarrassed these are all
things we're we're essentially trying to
avoid experiencing our past over and
over again and that's why it feels like
you got a pit in your stomach and you're
gonna throw up when you go to actually
build your business when you go to
actually
um do the things that you're trying to
do and so that's why
you have to get to the root of like
where did that belief come from sit with
it Journal it out just a little bit
and realize that it's time for you to
stop letting fear and worry and what
could go wrong stop you the other thing
is this technology isn't going to hurt
you you're not gonna lose money you
can't break it it's not the nuclear
codes
technology have a lot of fail safes now
built into them to make it to where you
don't have to be perfect and know how
everything fits together to be able to
use it it's very user friendly for
people and it's designed now because
most of society is not very tech savvy
most of the technology now is actually
designed to be 10 times easier than it
ever has been in just the last two years
and so if you haven't used technology in
a while realize that most of the tech
that's out there now is simple enough
for you to use if you know how to use
email Facebook Instagram Twitter uh
you'll be able to to to use most all of
the technology that you need to
successfully grow a course or coaching
business
and so your goal is you need to actually
identify
your Niche what is a problem that you
solve who are you helping with something
maybe you got too many ideas pick one or
two or three and put them together and
make that be a super Niche that you
could go into and then identify what's a
goal what's a dream
that you want
to deliver what's a dream that the type
of person that you can coach wants that
they just absolutely desire more than
anything else
can you promise that to the person that
you're coaching can you promise the
dreams that your clients have back to
them
that's what you're going to want to do
and and you're going to want to be very
specific
about who you help what their problem is
like to the point of like I'm a life
coach to video Gamers who are struggling
with fortnite right like a very specific
game and they need a mental health coach
like you could build a whole business
just around that right there and it
would be awesome you probably would have
to play fortnite a little bit but
um and so realize that
any one of you if you're listening this
right now you can make six figures as a
coach or in a
course or coaching business
because
it's not complicated it's not hard
anymore
if we can break up with hesitation
hesitating
to try out a new piece of software
hesitating to create a free account a
free trial to try out some of the
software and put something together
if you're afraid of losing time or
you're afraid of it just not working out
or not going your way that's common for
most people most people fear things not
working out
I want you to start to become more
curious
like a child
to where you're curious to see will it
work out is there something I can learn
about how it can work out and is there
something that this experience is
actually growing and creating inside of
me
that perspective will
make your dreams come true
that's what I help people with in my
coaching program is if they want to
write their offer copy and create their
landing pages and put all that
technology together you get access to me
to work with you
through everything step by step to walk
alongside you that you don't have to do
it all on your own you got me in your
corner you got me on your team to work
with
and that's what my coaching program is
is I'm on your team to get you success I
want to create over a thousand
millionaire coaches and that's going to
start by us being on the same team
together
okay so if you're listening to this
right now again please share this
podcast with somebody I know that it
will impact them
like it's going to impact you as well
you have to start by setting up an
account with squarespace.com
and then set up an account with
jasper.ai we have a free trial if you go
to jeremiahkrakowski.com forward slash
Jasper you'll find that free trial
and you want to start to use these two
pieces of technology to create a page on
a Squarespace site if you're in my
coaching program we have courses and
training and coaching where we'll come
alongside you and actually help walk you
through every single step
of putting your funnel together every
single step of mapping out your copy and
how it all fits together that's included
with the with the coaching program and
enrollment
as of the time of this recording in 2022
is
one thousand nine hundred ninety seven
dollars for the year less than
166.42 cents a month I think that's a
steal for what you get by working with
me if you're connected with me there's
no reason for you to struggle in your
coaching business there's no reason for
you to be stuck because I've seen every
scenario that you could possibly go
through or imagine two to three times
over before
and I know how to get past everything to
get you to six figures and a seven
figures
you you were born to Be a Millionaire
coach I want you to believe that
I want you to believe that you were born
to Be a Millionaire coach
start thinking that way even if that
stretches your
insides you're like man I can't see
myself being a millionaire
I just want a simple life
the methods that I teach
are not for the tiny the small they're
there to generate at least a million
dollars as a coach and as a course
creator
and so
start to sit with why are you stalling
to take action to try out different
technology why do you freeze why do you
shut down what are you really afraid of
start to sit with and try to answer that
and realize it's not dangerous it's not
going to hurt you it's not going to come
out to you you're not going to break
anything
you gotta quit if I could just shake you
through the camera you got to quit
hesitating
you gotta quit stalling
and coming up with good reasons and
excuses why now isn't your right season
if it's finances go find somebody to
invest in you
go find somebody to invest in your
business go find somebody who believes
in the vision for you in your life
if it's time learn to prioritize your
time differently
you know for you to reach your goals you
might have to leave certain friends and
situations behind and that's by Design
to start to grow your email list and and
get some people on a live call with you
that you can coach that you can connect
with and that and that you can ask
what's your problem what are you going
through what's struggling you with what
are you dealing
around
and people will answer these questions
for you and and the words that they give
you because you want to get feedback
from people the whole reason that you're
doing this is to facilitate other people
to give you feedback other people to
tell you what are they struggling with
your goal is to get people
that have the problem that you solve to
tell you in their own words what's
bothering them and then you build those
words into the artificial intelligence
marketing
that way you can make sales and
marketing the Supreme priority in your
business
you're gonna impact more people by
making more money
it's so obvious
when you put it together and I've been
doing this long enough that I can tell
you if you're still listening to this
right now you can become a millionaire
as a coach it's not going to be easy
there's going to be some hard choices
you got to make there's gonna be some
hard decisions there's gonna be some
things that you got to do differently
and one of those is you need to invest
into a mentor
invest into your own coach to help guide
you to help call you up to help you get
unstuck so that you keep moving forward
and and I would love to help you and be
that coach for you
you can get on the waiting list for my
coaching program over at my website for
the client growth accelerator
there's no reason for you to hesitate to
stall you can figure something out in
the next 30 days
you can figure something out in the next
two weeks how to get going I get it we
all got stuff that's happening in our
life and I'm not trying to be
insensitive to that I might have
somebody that died in the family you
might have lost a pet you might have had
something crazy happen it's okay
grieving loss helps us rise stronger
sometimes we need to we need to actually
grieve what once was
grieve what we wish how things were
and that allows us to step up
to a higher level
of influence impact and income in our
businesses
you have experiences in your life
that can help change somebody else's
life you have experiences in your life
that you can coach somebody else on and
then you could charge
300 500
a thousand dollars for coaching to
somebody
around something that just from your
life experience you can help walk them
through who's dealing with the same
thing
and that's what I Mentor you on is how
to put that together how to build those
offers how to write that copy how to how
to then find that person with ads and
connect with them it's all in the offer
copy it's all in the language the ads
are not about the tech and the ad
platform it's very simple it's very easy
the ads are about the words that you
write in the offer the words that
describe the problem the person has
so let's say like video gamers are
looking for a life coach you could say
you know are you are you struggling to
excel at life while you play video games
do you want to hit higher scores in life
and in the game
you know
are you ready to go from being a beta to
an alpha
you might pull in some guys that want
want that with that type of language
around video games
speaking to and what's their own
language are you do you are you tired of
just living life in the back seat of
your life and do you want to start to
create your life
design your life and get it moving
forward
and say you want to listen to what are
people going through you your your
entire goal behind doing a zoom call
behind doing a live event is just to
listen to people for people to tell you
what are they dealing with
the whole goal is you just want to
listen to people to then create offers
that they want and your coaching program
is going to be based around those offers
okay it's not complicated it's not
rocket science anybody listening to this
can do this
you don't need case studies
you don't need anything that proves
you're an expert
you create an offer that makes a promise
of some kind of a result to somebody and
without case studies if it's free you'll
have people take you up on it
you'll have people that will at least
try you out because it's free
and then that will build case studies
initially you might have a beta test
group
now you're going to want to talk about
your life experiences you want to
validate somehow how you learn this even
if you learned it from a book you've
listened to a bunch of podcasts and you
know how to guide and you're maybe you
and you're a coach and you're just
you're somebody that helps coach people
like that's fine you don't need to
actually have a track record to be able
to do this and most people think that
but you need to start making money and
you need to get out of your own way of
hesitating
to build the things that you need to
build in your business
sign up for Squarespace it's free
sign up for a free trial of Jasper use
chat GPT to start to write your
marketing and put it together
there is no reason to stay stuck for
longer than the next two weeks
at all
if you're connected with me you can ask
me questions I'm here to help you I'm
here to guide you and I'm here to lead
you to become a millionaire coach
thousand people I want to help become
millionaires as coaches and so
I'll help you get there if you take the
action
okay
listen thanks for listening to this
podcast if this has helped you at all
share it with somebody we want to help
so many people get their message out
to get more customers to get more
clients to make more money than they
ever imagined like the clients that
we're helping like the people that we've
worked with that have created insane
results million dollar months
like my client Rick
over a million dollars one month
you can do that as well
all right
so share this podcast with somebody that
grow Your Life podcast subscribe listen
to it check out our YouTube channel
there's over a thousand videos under the
live Tab and YouTube for free that'll
help you there's almost there's 195
episodes of this podcast
that'll help you grow in your business
and then consider if you want some
guidance my coaching program
if it's not currently open in enrollment
right now and next year it's going to
cost more than two thousand dollars but
if it's not open enrollment while you're
listening to this right now get on the
waiting list for the next time that we
open it okay
and then we'll keep
keep moving things forward that way all
right
you can do this there's no reason to be
stuck there's no reason to stay stuck
unless you are basically choosing to
stay stuck there's no good reason you
can come up with why you would stay
stuck other than you don't want to move
forward that's it
okay
that's not to invalidate you but that's
just because I'm here to help Mentor you
and I'm here to help guide you and and
I'm committed to your success
and so take advantage of that take
advantage of me take advantage of my
kindness
to help guide you to success we'll talk
soon have a good one
[Music]
[Applause]